这个问题的答案是ListPreference.当设置
The solution to this question is ListPreference. When the setting
被点击后，一列选择被展示出来作为
is tapped, it presents a list of choices as a
一个对话框，当用户选择一个选项，它被保存进入
dialogue. When a user selects an option, it's saved into
SharedPreferences。这是做这件事的步骤：在
SharedPreferences. Here are the steps to do this. Within
pref_general.xml这个文件里我们加入了一列选项。我们赋值给
the pref_general.xml file we add a list preference. We give
它们一个title，这与气温单位匹配。
it a title, and this maps to the string temperature
我们还需要赋给它一个键值给
units. We also need to give it a key for
SharedPreferences。然后我们指明是作为单位的。
the SharedPreferences. And so we specify that to be units.
如果SharedPreferences中没有值，它将会
If there is no value in SharedPreferences, then it
显示公制的默认值。这个选项
falls back to a default value of metric. The preference
也倾向于了解所有的可能值。
also wants to know the list of all possible values
两个可能值是米制或英制。所以我们
here. The two possible values are metric or imperial. So we
把他们以数组传递进条目。现在
pass those in as an array, into entry values. Now
这些仅仅是用到的常量在
these are just constants for use within the logic of our
我们程序的逻辑中，并非用户可见的变量。所以我们
app, these are not the user visible strings. So we
需要创建用户可见的数组条目
need to create entries which is an array of user visible
字符串匹配每一个可能值。
strings that maps to each one of these possible values. To
为了使气温单位选项在设置这一活动里显示
have the temperature unit preference show up in the settings activity,
我们在onCreate方法中进行修改。我们添加这一行
we modify the on create method. We add this line of
代码在气温单位设定里。当用户做出一个
code for the temperature units setting. When the user makes a
选择在对话框中，我们设定选项为
selection in the dialog, we set the preference summary to be
为公制或英制。因此，当我们
the new value of either metric or imperial. Here, when we
获取一个最高气温一个最低气温，我们从SharedPreferences中
receive a high and low temperature, we read from SharedPreferences
得知气温是否要被转成英制或者
to know whether the temperature should be converted to imperial units or
直接保留为公制。然后我们将格式设定完成的的字符串返回用以显示给
left as metric. Then we return the formatted string for display in
用户界面。保存天气单位设定的代码完成。
the UI. That completes the code for saving the temperature unit setting.